三个月前
天啊
Oh, my God.
救我
Help me.
黑吃黑
第四季
第二集
求你  不要
No, please.
求你不要
Please don't.
不要  求你了
Please don't. Please.
求你  不要
Please don't. No.
不要  不要
No. No, please.
不要
No.
求你了  求你了
Please. Please. Please. Please.
住手
Stop.
卡
Cut!
大家继续
Moving on, people.
-准备拍特写  -镇警署
- Let's reset for close-up. - Sheriff's Department.
-你他妈干什么  -你们被捕了
- What the fuck are you doing? - You're all under arrest.
你胡说什么  我们有拍摄执照
The fuck are you talking about? This is a licensed production.
你做的这种事没有执照  混蛋
There's no license for what you're doing here, asshole.
上帝  伙计  把裤子穿上
Jesus Christ, son, pull your pants up.
你没事吧  看着我
You all right? Look at me.
你多大
How old are you?
别回答  这是天大的误会
Don't answer that. You're making a big mistake.
别他妈碰我
Don't fucking touch me.
邦克  把他们抓起来
Bunker, I want you to arrest all these people.
-什么都不要说  -我操
- Don't fucking say anything. - Shit, fuck!
尽管拒捕  就当给我个理由
Go ahead, resist. Give me a reason, huh?
快跑
Run!
去死  贱货
Fuck you, bitch!
庞尼·乔
Pony Joe.
你个混蛋
Motherfucker.
我说过你被捕了吗
Have I mentioned you're under arrest?
去死  叛徒
Fuck you, traitor.
分开关  给我分开录口供
Split 'em up. I need individual statements.
导演关哪
Where do you want the director?
带去审讯室
Put him in the interrogation room.
暖气打开
Turn up the heat.
-我想见我的律师  -好好
- I want to talk to my lawyer. - Yeah, yeah.
早上好  警长
Good morning, Sheriff.
市长先生  你坐了我的椅子
Mr. Mayor, you're in my chair.
听说你和警官们今早很忙啊
I heard you and your deputies had a busy morning.
如果地检无法定罪  逮捕就毛用没有
Arrests don't mean shit if your DA can't get a conviction.
不会有问题
That won't be a problem.
没错  我想也是
Yeah, I guess it won't.
我不是白痴
I'm not an idiot.
你当我不知道  你的克鲁兹小姑娘
You think I don't know that every time your girl Cruz
每次得到匿名线报  其实都是我们在替你干脏活
gets an anonymous tip, we're doing your dirty work?
你很清楚是谁让你坐上这个位子
I don't need to remind you who put you in charge here
又帮你保住位子的吧  要我提醒吗
and kept you in charge, do I?
请问有什么吩咐  市长先生
What can I do for you, Mr. Mayor?
我侄女的谋杀案有什么进展了
What progress have you made on my niece's murder investigation?
有几条线索
We have a few leads.
我知道  我看过卷宗了
Yeah, I read through the files.
这些卷宗都是机密文件
These files are confidential.
你别忘了
And in case you forgot,
你也是这个案子的嫌疑人
you're still a person of interest in this case.
如果我不是去
And if I wasn't out there
忙活着帮你关电影场子
wasting my time shutting down fuck films for you,
现在可能都抓到这三起谋杀案的疑犯了
I'd have arrested a suspect in all three murders by now.
此后你每天都跟我汇报最新进展
I expect daily updates from now on.
是吗  那不是克鲁兹副警长的职责吗
Really? I thought that was Deputy Cruz's job.
我要听你跟我汇报  布罗克
I want them from you, Brock.
那我一定优先处理  市长先生
Then I will make it a top priority, Mr. Mayor.
打扰了  谢谢
Thank you for your time.
不客气
You're welcome.
你好
Hi.
你看起来不错
You look good.
去你的
Fuck you.
这里有多少土地  10英亩吗
So what do you have here, 10 acres?
25英亩
25.
树林也是我的
The woods are mine, too.
安静平和
It's peaceful.
只属于我
It's private.
谢谢
Thanks.
新地方不错
New place is great.
还在改建
A work in progress.
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
我需要点时间
I guess I needed some time.
恩  我也需要
Yeah, I could have used some, too.
我不该背弃你
I shouldn't have turned my back on you.
你背弃的不仅是我
You didn't turn your back on just me.
-贾伯死了  -为什么  因为道尔顿这么说吗
- Job's dead. - Why, because Dalton said so?
不  贾伯这样的人
No, because that's what they do
栽在他们手里就是这个下场
with people like Job.
你不能肯定
You didn't know.
所有地方都找遍了
There was nowhere left to look.
潜在线索  跟踪警长
无结果
你一直在找他
You kept looking for him.
是的
Yes.
但没找到
Still nothing.
没
No.
蒂法怎么样了
What about Deva?
你连见她一面都不想吗
Didn't you at least want to see her?
我见过她了
I have seen her.
她没告诉我
She didn't tell me.
她知道如果告诉你  你会想过来
She knew if she did, you'd want to come.
蒂法背着你去  让你觉得是背叛吗
And Deva going behind your back feels like a betrayal?
我只是  我要保护她
I just-- I need to protect her.
-以防被他伤害  -以防任何伤害
- From him? - From everything.
-那不可能  卡莉  -以前都这样
- That's not possible, Carrie. - It used to be.
安娜
Ana.
在他出现在女妖镇
Before he showed up in Banshee
强迫进入你的生活以前吗
and forced himself back into your life?
-我没这么说过  -但你这么觉得  不是吗
- I didn't say that. - But that's what you feel, isn't it?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
为什么
For what?
所有事
Everything.
你遭受的损失  承受的痛苦
The losses you've suffered, the pain you've endured,
别人选择  你承担后果
all the result of a choice made by someone else.
而现在他再一次出现了  就像两年前一样
And now he's back again, showing up like he did two years before.
如果你真的在意我的损失和痛苦
If you're so concerned about my losses and pain,
那就让我的孩子们回到我身边吧
why don't you let my kids come home to me?
-我们讨论过这事了  卡莉  -再讨论一下
- We've already discussed this, Carrie. - Let's discuss it again.
我能做的只有提出建议
All I can do is make a recommendation.
除此之外  无可奈何
Beyond that, my hands are tied.
那我他妈来这儿干嘛
Then what the fuck am I doing here?
告诉我谁能做决定
Tell me who gets to make that choice
让我去跟他们谈
and let me go talk to them.
这太扯淡了
This is bullshit.
我们谈谈戈登吧
Let's talk about Gordon.
谈他什么
What about him?
你开始整理他的东西了吗
Have you started sorting through his belongings?
没有
No.
卡莉  你等得越久
The longer you wait, Carrie--
怎么
What?
就越困难
The harder it gets?
相信我  这他妈不能再难了
Trust me, it can't get any fucking harder.
把最后三个托盘装好
Hey, get those last three pallets loaded.
几小时前就该运走了
That truck should have been on the road hours ago.
混蛋
Motherfucker.
普罗科特先生  您今天怎么来了
Mr. Proctor, I was not expecting you today.
我向您的亲人表示哀悼...
My condolences on your loss--
退下
Don't.
我认为我们约定得很清楚
I'd say our terms of agreement were pretty clear.
你和你的兄弟们运营我的产业
You and your Brotherhood manage my operations
而我允许你们保留自己的生意  获取利润
and I permit you to maintain yours for a bit of your profits.
我们一直照此执行
And that's what you've been getting.
我亲自负责查帐
I check the accounting myself.
因此你要为出现的错误负责
Which is why I hold you responsible for any errors.
包括疏漏
Or omissions for that matter.
-你一直在做副业  -普罗科特先生
- You've been running a side business. - Mr. Proctor--
今早是我唯一一次警告
What happened this morning was your one and only warning...
邦克先生
Mr. Bunker.
从现在起  我的份额升到百分之十
From now on, my cut goes up by 10%.
你想让我跟沃茨先生说说我们的新约定吗
Do you want me to talk to Mr. Watts about our new terms?
没有这个必要
That won't be necessary.
我觉得也是
I didn't think so.
审讯的事你打算怎么处理
What are you going to do about the arraignment?
我为什么要处理这个
Why should I do anything?
我的人很可靠  我可以担保
My men are solid. I can vouch for them,
但导演是个自由职业者
but the director's a freelancer.
保不准他为了自救会出卖谁
There's no telling who he'd rat out to save his own ass.
邦克先生  看来你下定决心要展示你的愚笨
Mr. Bunker, you seem determined to prove your ineptitude.
我会处理此事
I'll deal with it.
来个人把这堆破玩意收拾好
Somebody pick this shit up.
你好像不太乐意见到我
You don't seem happy to see me.
三个月前
你还好吗
How are you?
好得不能再好了
Never better.
很好  我需要你帮忙
Good, cause I need your help.
帮什么
With what?
你听过亚伦·博迪克这个名字吗
You ever heard of Aaron Boedicker?
听过  一个毒品贩子
Yeah, a meth dealer.
他和他的团伙以前只在山里贩毒
He and his clan used to just cook up in the foothills,
但现在他们开始在镇子里卖了
but now they've started selling it in town.
听起来是普罗科特的麻烦
Sounds like a problem for Proctor.
不  其实是我的麻烦
No, it's actually a problem for me.
他们很有制毒经验
They were experienced cooks and I was looking
而我一直在试着拓展自己的渠道
to branch out on my own a little bit.
我警告过博迪克不准碰女妖镇
I warned Boedicker that Banshee was off-limits.
我猜猜  近亲繁殖的毒贩子
Let me guess, the inbred drug dealer
不听24岁的姑娘的命令
didn't listen to the 24-year-old girl.
我是求你帮我搞定这事
I'm asking you to help me fix this.
我舅舅如果发现我做的事  我就死定了
My uncle finds out what I've done, I'm dead.
-求你了  -不关我的事
- Please? - It's not my problem.
你在破旧的汽车旅馆房
You drinking yourself to death
喝得烂醉也不关我的事
in a shithole motel room wasn't my problem either.
你帮不帮忙我都会追查博迪克
I'm going after Boedicker with or without you.
我只是想有你帮忙  我胜算更大
I just thought that with you I'd have an actual chance.
内有恶犬
站住
Stop!
把枪放下  贱人
Drop the gun, bitch.
你把枪放下  混蛋
You drop yours, asshole.
他凭什么要放下枪
Why the hell would he do that?
如果他不放下
'Cause if he doesn't,
我会一枪打爆你的狗头
I'm gonna blow your fucking head off.
既然你诚心诚意地发问了
Well, since you asked so nicely...
没事了  孩子  有我在
It's okay, son, I got this.
把他弄走
Get him out of here.
所以这是串门吗
So, is this a social call?
因为我可能记性不好
'Cause my memory could be failing me,
但我真不记得有请你过来
but I don't remember inviting you to visit.
你没请
You didn't.
那你就是非法入侵我的领地
Then you're trespassing on my land.
我们有约在先
We had a deal.
你一直在分钱
You've been getting your cut.
我说的是你不能在女妖镇出货
The deal was you wouldn't sell meth in Banshee.
你知不知道
Do you have any idea what
我舅舅知道了会怎么收拾你
my uncle would do to you if he found out?
我一点也不喜欢别人对我指手划脚
I never much liked being told what to do.
那你肯定不喜欢我一枪崩了你
Then you're really gonna hate it when I shut you down.
狗屁  小姑娘
Shit, girl,
别在那儿痴人说梦了
that there just ain't never gonna happen.
莱姆  把她弄进去
Lem, get the girl inside.
我要和她好好聊聊
She and I need to have a little chin-wag.
我想你还不明白
I don't think you appreciate
自己惹了多大麻烦  小姑娘
how much trouble you're in, little girl.
他最好别再动我
He'd better not touch me again.
而我不知道
And I don't know what I
当时怎么会答应跟你做交易
was thinking getting into business with you.
是你违背了协议
You're the one who broke the agreement.
漂亮女孩的毛病就是
The problem with being a pretty girl
你们往往会觉得
is that over time you get the idea
说什么  做什么都可以随心所欲
that you can do or say whatever the fuck you want.
我可以帮你个忙
I'm gonna do you a favor.
我可以帮你摆脱美丽的负担
I'm gonna remove the burden of beauty.
海瑟前阵子叼回了只患狂犬病的负鼠
Hesher here chased down a rabid possum a while back.
之后它就变了个样
He ain't been the same since.
天啊
Jesus.
你个臭婊子
You fucking bitch.
苍天啊
Oh... Jesus Christ!
你没事吧  看着我  看着我
You okay? Look at me. Look at me.
走
Come on.
丽贝卡  丽贝卡
Rebecca! Rebecca!
丽贝卡
Hey, Rebecca.
我们没时间了
We don't have time for this.
丽贝卡
Rebecca.
趴下
Get down!
邦克
Bunker.
我没想到你会泡这种酒吧
Not the kind of bar I would think you'd hang out in.
你不知道的还有很多
There's a lot you don't know about me.
没错  先生
I'm sure that's true, sir.
在这个酒吧喝酒犯法了吗
Is there a law against drinking in this bar?
警长让我要你等着
The sheriff asked me to ask you to wait.
等什么
Wait for what?
我让他跟你说
I'll let him tell you.
-车不错  -谢了
- Nice car. - Thanks.
你在这干什么  胡德
What are you doing here, Hood?
我渴了  想喝杯啤酒
I was thirsty. Thought I might get a beer.
你不是来调查鲍曼被杀案的吗
You're not here investigating the Bowman murder?
不是  长官  我说过我退休了
No, sir. I told you, I'm retired.
好  听着
Yeah, yeah, listen.
有人在杀年轻姑娘
Someone's out there killing young girls
我现在压力有点大
and I'm a little under the gun here,
所以再问你一次  你来这干什么
so I'm gonna ask you again, what are you doing here?
乐队里有个小子对丽贝卡有意思
One of the guys in the band had a thing with Rebecca.
我想看看表演  认识认识
I figured I'd watch the show, introduce myself.
不  你在这等着  我和邦克去跟他谈
No, you wait here. Bunker and I will go talk to him.
那小子是个山区毒贩
Kid's a hillbilly drug dealer.
看到穿制服的就会跑
He's gonna run as soon as he sees the uniforms.
那我们就知道该抓哪个了
Then we'll know which one to grab.
咱们走  邦克
Let's go, Bunker.
抱歉
Sorry.
-让开  -伙计
- Get out of the way! - Ow, man!
让开
Get out of the way.
-邦克  -看着点
- Bunker! - Look!
在这儿
Here!
闭嘴
Shut up.
蛇眼酒吧
胡德
Hood!
妈的
God damn it.
请进
Come in.
富兰克林先生  请坐
Mr. Franklin. Do you wanna sit down?
-你想要见我  -是的
- You wanted to see me? - Yes.
我看了
I've been going through
色情片一案的案件资料
the case file from the pornography arrests.
凯·普罗科特
证据很明显
The evidence is overwhelming.
我很有信心给五位嫌疑人定罪
I'll have no problem getting convictions for all five defendants.
-撤销诉讼  -什么
- Withdraw the charges. - What?
-为什么  -我有自己的理由
- Why? - I have my reasons.
先生  恕我直言
Sir, with all due respect,
你之前要我严惩这些家伙的
you told me to throw the book at these guys.
现在我告诉你  放了他们
And now I'm telling you to let them go.
普罗科特先生  如果我们继续这样做
Mr. Proctor, there's only so many times we can do this
不用多久人们就会质疑我们了
before people start asking questions.
-这是我操心的事情  -先生  坦白说
- I'll worry about that. - Sir, frankly,
-我不明白  -你操心我就好了
- I don't understand-- - and you worry about me.
-还有其他事情吗  -没有  先生
- Was there anything else? - No, sir.
谢谢你接见我
Thank you for your time.
他不会是问题
He won't be a problem.
坐吧
Take a seat.
我他妈来这儿干嘛
What the fuck am I doing here?
我让你他妈的坐下来
I said take a fucking seat.
丽贝卡·鲍曼出了什么事了
What happened to Rebecca Bowman?
我他妈怎么知道  我还坐在这儿干什么
How the fuck should I know? Why am I even sitting here?
你都不是警察了
You're not even a cop anymore.
是的
That's right.
所以我不管怎么凑你  也不会被停职
That means I can kick your fucking head in and not get fired.
你把我拖到这儿的  你他妈怎么不...
You dragged me here. Why don't you go fuck yourself--
不然呢
Or...
好吧
All right. All right.
我喜欢丽贝卡
I liked Rebecca.
我们曾经好过
We had a good thing going.
后来她甩了你吗
Till she dumped you?
她没甩我
She didn't dump me.
后来事情变复杂了
Things just got complicated.
怎么个复杂法
Complicated how?
-给我个啤酒什么的  -不行
- Can I get a beer or something? - No.
怎么个复杂法
Complicated how?
我就不应该跟她提我叔叔
I should have never told her about my fucking uncle.
亚伦·博迪克
Aaron Boedicker?
-他们在做生意  对吗  -她曾是他的客户
- They did some business, right? - She was his business.
在她介入前  他一直在浴缸里制毒
He was cooking that junk up in his bathtub before she got involved.
只要他不在女妖镇贩卖
She's the one that gave him cash
她就会给他钱
as long as he didn't deal in Banshee.
那是他们谈好的
That was the deal.
-我跟她说了他不会照做  -他没照做
- I told her he wouldn't stick with it. - And he didn't.
从那时起
That's when she started
她就开始神经兮兮  疑心一切了
acting all crazy paranoid about everything.
我以为她害怕我的家人
I thought that she was scared of my family,
但她说  他们什么都不是
but she said they were nothing.
她害怕的是普罗科特
It was Proctor that scared the shit out of her.
她告诉我  那家伙就是个变态
The twisted shit she told me about him.
哥们  你完全不知道那家伙有多坏
Man, you have no idea how fucked up that guy really is.
你想知道丽贝卡发生了什么吗
You wanna know what happened to Rebecca?
去问那个混蛋
Ask that motherfucker.
好吧  走吧
All right, go.
滚蛋
Get the fuck out of here.
看来这姑娘的鬼魂让你整个人都乱套了
Seems this girl's ghost has got you all out of sorts.
我欠她一份人情
Yeah, I owed her one.
一定是很大的人情
Must have been a real big one.
你想说什么  直说好了
You got something to say, just say it.
好像你欠贾伯比
Seems like you owe Job
比欠这个女的要多啊
a lot more than you owe this girl.
我还就说出来了
There, now I've said it.
普罗科特先生
Senor Proctor.
欢迎来宾州  洛埃拉先生
Welcome to Pennsylvania, Mr. Loera.
关于你侄女
About your niece.
[西语]
你该花时间去哀悼  生意可以暂缓
You should take time to mourn. Business can wait.
正好相反
On the contrary.
生命可以停止  但生意一定要继续
A life can stop, but business must go on.
自从上次谈过后  我的生意成倍的增长
My operation's been growing exponentially since we last talked.
扩张我的销售网是我的优先目标
Expanding my distribution network is of high priority.
-我有什么好处  -市场统治
- How does that benefit me? - Market dominance.
锡那罗和中国人的合伙关系
It's no secret that the Sinaloa's partnership
伤到了你的价格底线  这已不是什么秘密
with the Chinese has hurt your bottom line.
一旦贩毒集团进入制药产业
Once the cartels got into the pill industry,
你就不能像你以往控制
you could no longer control the market pricing
可卡因和海洛因那样控制市场价格了
like you did with the cocaine and the heroin.
他们跨越边境运送货物
They're moving product across the border--
运货量比率比你高两倍  价格却低很多
twice your rate, just a fraction of the price.
日益增加的交易给你带来了
The increased traffic is just causing you
更多的边界难题
even more border headaches.
我可以提供一个当地渠道  没有任何风险
I can offer a local pipeline without any of the risk
还能省掉从哥伦比亚进口产品的费用
or expense of having to import the product itself from Colombia.
恕我直言  但我的交易量
No disrespect, but I deal in a very different volume
和你在宾州的交易量有很大不同
than you do here in Pennsylvania.
我佩服你的野心
Your ambition impresses me,
但我不觉得你玩得起我这种级别
but I'm not convinced that you can play in my league.
那就让我来说服你
Then allow me to convince you.
很好  14天后你给我
Very well. I expect three tons
准备好三吨的货
ready for pickup in 14 days.
没问题
Done.
当这次交易完成时
When this transaction is completed,
我希望能成为你东海岸的独家供货商
I expect to be your exclusive East Coast supplier.
成交吗
Do we have a deal?
普罗科特先生  我听说过传闻
Senor Proctor, I've heard the stories.
你是个危险人物
You're a dangerous man.
但一个女妖镇的危险人物
But a dangerous man in Banshee,
在贩毒集团面前  不过是只蚊子
to the cartel, is still nothing but a mosquito.
决不允许交货失败
Failure to deliver is not an option.
两周后见
I'll see you in two weeks.
我看了下指控  看起来都合乎程序
I reviewed the complaint. All seems to be in order.
你准备好提议保释金额了吗  富兰克林先生
Are you prepared to make a bond recommendation, Mr. Franklin?
此
At, um--
此时此刻  法官大人  检方希望
at this time, Your Honor, the people would like
撤销对所有五个被告的指控
to withdraw their complaint against all five defendants.
我们说的是同一起案件吗  辩护人
Are we discussing the same case here, Counselor?
似乎有充分理由可以起诉
There seems to be more than sufficient cause here to proceed.
是的  法官大人  然而
Yes, Your Honor, however,
检方最近新发现了
the people have recently discovered
证据不一致
new evidentiary inconsistencies
以及女妖镇警署可能
and possible Miranda violations
违反了米兰达权利
on the part of the Banshee Sheriff's Department.
鉴于这些令人遗憾的新发现
In light of these unfortunate developments,
我们只能撤销指控  放弃起诉
we have no choice but to vacate the charges and decline prosecution.
好的
Very well.
我想辩方应该不会反对吧
I take it there are no objections from the defense?
-不会  法官大人  -动议批准
- No, Your Honor. - Motion granted.
所有指控全部撤销
All charges are dismissed.
立即释放这些人
These men are to be released from custody immediately.
我自由了  可以回家了
I am free. Home and free.
公诉人先生  请到内庭来
Mr. Prosecutor, I'd like a word in my chambers.
邦克  你还好吗
Hey, Bunker. How you doing?
不敢相信这家伙就这么被释放了
I can't believe this guy's back on the street.
他请的大多数演员都是未成年
Most of his actresses are underage.
他不仅给她们拍片  还下药强奸她们
He doesn't just shoot them, he drugs them and rapes them.
很高兴又见到你  霍普韦尔夫人
Nice to see you again, Mrs. Hopewell.
12个月前
发生了什么
What happened?
我在清理我的东西
I'm having my things removed.
我觉得你会想重新装修你的新办公室
I thought you'd want to redecorate your new office.
谢了  舅舅
Thank you, Uncle.
客气
You're welcome.
亚伦·博迪克没有杀丽贝卡
Aaron Boedicker didn't kill Rebecca.
-你确定吗  -确定
- Are you sure? - I'm sure.
她之前在睡他侄子
She was fucking his nephew.
你知情吗
Did you know that?
她和谁睡与我无关
Who she fucked is none of my business.
我相信你一有别的发现就会通知我
I trust you'll keep me informed of anything else you find out.
要是我发现凶手是你呢
What if I find out it was you?
我没什么好掩藏的
I got nothing to hide.
女妖镇警署  谋杀案档案  复印件
什么事
Yeah?
司法鉴定报告出来了
Forensics report came back from the lab.
在丽贝卡·鲍曼车上
There was a positive match to
找到的血样  发现配对的人了
the blood sample we found in Rebecca Bowman's SUV.
三个月前
救命
Help me.
胡德
Hood.
-王八蛋  -这不能说明他就是凶手
- Son of a bitch. - It doesn't make him a killer.
是  但绝对能说明他是个骗子
Yeah, well, it sure as shit makes him a liar.
亲爱的  你现在安全了
You're safe now, sweetie.
一切都会好起来的  我马上回来
Everything's gonna be okay. I'll be right back.
你不会真的认为是他干的吧
You don't really think he did it, do you?
我也不想
I don't want to,
但他和普罗科特关系一直都不怎么样
but he and Proctor have never been best buddies.
可能丽贝卡被夹在中间
You know, maybe Rebecca got caught up between them.
那也构不成谋杀的动机啊
That's not a motive for murder.
没有动机  就不能立案
Without that, we don't have a case.
对  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我们也找不到他和其他女孩有联系的证据
And we don't have anything connecting him to the other girls.
没有  我知道
No, I know. I know.
而且  你了解胡德
And also you know Hood.
我就是了解他  才会知道
I know Hood just well enough to know
我并不了解真正的他
that I don't know him at all.
你要抓他审问吗
Do you want me to bring him in?
不用  等一等
No, let's wait.
看看这条线索能把我们引向哪里
Let's see where this trail leads us.
好的
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
姑娘们  这边
Right this way, girls.
欢迎来到迪克·韦伯斯特影视制片公司
Welcome to Dick Webster Productions.
这里就是奇迹发生的地方
This is where the magic happens.
请坐  坐沙发上吧
I want you to sit down. Sit down on the couch.
自在点儿
Get comfortable.
你们想看看海报
You want to check out some of the posters
还是看看碟
or, you know, some of the DVDs?
我去弄点鸡尾酒
I'm gonna get us some cocktails
然后就开始试镜
and then we're gonna start the audition, okay?
我们喝伏特加吧
We're gonna make it vodka.
来吧  伙计
Yeah, buddy.
被你发现了  女士
You got me. You got me, lady.
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
关心社会的公民
A concerned citizen.
你最好别招惹我
I don't think you want to mess with me.
招的就是你
I do.
沃茨他妈的怎么能这么瞎
How can Watts be so fucking blind?
普罗科特把我们当黑奴使唤
Proctor's got us running around like niggers in the field
累活儿全让我们干了
doing all the hard work,
结果那个混蛋自己发大财
while that motherfucker just keeps getting richer.
可能被关久了
Maybe all that time in the cage
沃兹习惯被人使唤了  可老子不行
and Watts doesn't mind taking it up the ass, but I fucking do.
我受够了给别人当狗了
I'm done being everybody's bitch.
那你准备干什么
Yeah, what are you gonna do?
我要等待时机
I'm going to wait for the right moment
抓住机会
and then I'm going to fucking seize it.
我要提醒兄弟会
I'm going to remind the Brotherhood
我们是何人
who the fuck we are.
有时候我觉得只有我能看清
Sometimes I wonder if I'm the only one who sees
这个世界变得多癫狂
how batshit crazy this world has become.
-求你别杀我  -沃茨已失去方向了
- Please don't kill me. - Watts has lost his vision.
去他妈的沃茨
Fuck Watts.
我们的家庭处于危险中  朝不保夕
He doesn't care that our families are in danger,
他丝毫不在乎  但是我在乎
that our future is on the brink, but I do.
天佑勇者
Fortune favors the bold.
不择手段才能获得权力
Power comes from being willing to do whatever it takes.
杀了你就太便宜你了
Killing you would be much too easy.
不惜一切获得公正
Justice at any cost.
我会盯着你的
I'll be watching you.
有人吗
Hello?
谁在那儿
Who's there?
有人吗
Hello?
我不想找麻烦  普罗科特
I don't want any trouble, Proctor.
我没杀丽贝卡  我发誓
I didn't kill Rebecca. I swear to God.
自己跟上帝说去吧
You can tell Him that yourself.
求你了  求求你
Please. Please.
一周前